Three is the skies, four is the earth.
（土御門(つちみかど)）
三は天界　四は地上
そして 十二で世界を示す
And with twelve, you represent the world.
By attaching a special meaning to certain words,
特定の数に
意味を付加することで―
they can gain immense numbers.
“莫大(ばくだい)”という単位を
得られるということか
It's a good spell, but it's not Christian.
うまい術式だが
こいつは十字教ではない
It's from Pythagoras' Greek teachings back in the B.C. era.
紀元前のギリシャ系
ピタゴラス教団の理論だぞ
Since when did you guys accept the world from before the Son of God was born?
貴様たちは いつの間に―
神の子が生まれる以前の世界を
肯定したんだ？
チッ…
長期戦で こちらに得はないな
Nothing good will come from a drawn-out battle...
Too bad.
残念だな　繊細な術式を見ると
壊すのが惜しくなってくる
When you see something fragile, you almost regret destroying it!
～♪
#21 Testament
Learning Device
If those guys show up again...
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
次に あいつらが現れるとしたら…
I have only four minutes left on esper mode...
能力使用モードは
４分も残ってねえな
I'll bring that brat out of the darkness, no matter what.
あのガキだけでも
闇の中から連れ出す
The entire facility is clear.
（ﾃﾞﾆｽ）
全施設をクリア　誰もいませんね
I guess they're not here.
Reports are indicating terrorist activity.
（ﾏｲｸ）
報告では テロ活動の危険あり
This says they temporarily evacuated all staff and patients.
一時的に
全職員と患者を退避させたとあるな
（ﾃﾞﾆｽ）ンッ… 気づかれましたね
（ﾏｲｸ）マズイな
They noticed us, eh?
This is bad.
Is it a trap?
（ﾏｲｸ）
トラップの可能性は？
No, I can't detect any infra-red beams.
（ﾃﾞﾆｽ）
ワイヤー 赤外線ともに
確認できません
Took you long enough.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）遅かったじゃないか
（ﾏｲｸ）冥土帰し(ヘヴンキャンセラー)…
Heaven Canceler!
I don't have much time left, so let me cut to the chase.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
時間がないから 手短に言うよ
Ignore Kihara and run away.
木原(きはら)のもとを離れ 逃走しろ
そうしないと 君たちの命が危ない
Your lives are at risk, otherwise.
Are you serious?
本気で言っているのか？
You'll be crushed by Accelerator.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
君はアクセラレータにつぶされる
He won't hold back on you.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
今の彼は 一切の加減をしない
You must not face Accelerator.
君はアクセラレータに
会ってはならない　それだけさ
That's all.
フッ… 世まい言を
Nonsense.
I see.
（ｶｴﾙ医者）
そうか　死ぬなよ
死なないかぎりは助けてやる
Well, don't die.
As long as you don't die, I'll save you.
We have reports that people are losing consciousness in various parts of Japan.
（街頭ﾃﾚﾋﾞ:ｱﾅｳﾝｻｰ）
現在 突発的に意識を失う人が
出ているという報告が―
全国のあちこちから届いています
Police are doing their best to determine the cause,
警察では
原因の特定を急いでいますが
日本のみならず 海外の一部でも
被害があったという…
but it is also said that similar events have been occurring overseas as well.
そっちのほうにも
広がったってことね
So it's finally spreading, huh?
I only needed to suppress Academy City, though...
学園都市さえ制圧できれば
良かったけど
あっ ラストオーダー
Last Order?!
No, Kihara?
いや 木原か
Thank goodness, someone picked up.
（上条(かみじょう)）
良かった！
ようやく つながったな
I've heard this voice before...
この声 どこかで…
（上条）
今 ラストオーダーの
携帯にあった番号に―
I was calling every number on Last Order's phone.
片っ端から かけてんだ
You're the only one who responded.
応答したのは あんただけ
You might not understand the situation, but I need your help.
状況が分からないかもしれないが
協力してほしい
She's in danger!
あの子が危ないんだ
What's the situation?
どういう状況だ？
You were separated at that restaurant, right?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
そのレストランで別れたんだな？
あとは こっちで回収しておく
I'll take care of the rest.
You throw away that cell phone and go back to your normal life.
お前は その携帯を捨てて
さっさと一般人に戻れ
What are you talking about?
何言ってんだ？
俺も手伝うに決まってんだろう！
I'm going to help you.
お前は
第７学区の でかい鉄橋に行け
Head to the large railway bridge in the Seventh School District.
That's the rendezvous point we'd decided on earlier.
あそこが いざというときの
合流地点ってことになってる
If she's still running, that's where she'd be headed.
あいつが今も逃げてんなら そこだ
（上条）ああ　分かった！
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）ンッ…
Got it!
Academy City's a bit strange today.
なんか
今日の学園都市は少し おかしい
There's some strange woman from out of town invading.
変なヤツが
街の外から侵入してきてるし
And on top of that, Anti-skill and normal citizens are all collapsing.
警備員(アンチスキル)とか街の人が
バタバタと倒れてるし
It seems like an indiscriminate assault, so you be careful, too.
かなり無差別な攻撃みたいだから
お前も気をつけろよ
チッ… 面倒くせえ
What a pain.
Sorry.
（上条）
悪いな　本当なら あの子は
ひとりにするべきじゃなかった
I shouldn't have left her alone.
We're even then.
お互いさまだ
I left her alone, too, after all...
俺も あのガキを
ひとりにしちまったからな
We've lost contact with multiple squads.
（隊員Ａ）
複数の班から連絡が途絶えました
恐らくは…
They've most likely...
They ran or they died.
（木原）
逃げたか 死んだか
どっちにしても
あとで心臓を集めねえとな
Either way, I'll have to gather their hearts later.
Did you recover the guys we used as decoys when that woman came?
（木原）
女がジャマに入ったときに
囮(おとり)に使った連中は回収できたか？
Yes.
（隊員Ａ）
はい　何らかの力が働いて―
It seems like some reaction has occurred.
The oxygen levels in their bodies are very low.
体内の酸素が
極端に減っているようです
An artificially induced asphyxiation...
人工的な仮死の誘発？
チッ… あの女の仕業か
The work of that woman, huh?
クッ… くそ！
Damn it!
All because of that bitch—
あんなヤツのせいで
オラフやルルも…
Hey!
Damn it, how is she targeting them?
野郎…
どうやって狙いをつけてやがる？
Wait, could it be unrelated to science?
いや まさか 非科学か？
Whatever, we'll do what we have to do.
まあいい！　こっちは
こっちのことをやるだけだ
Is the Testament ready?
（木原）学習装置(テスタメント)の用意は？
（隊員Ｂ）はい
Yes.
Right here.
（隊員Ｂ）
こちらに
あっ… これは あいつの…
That's... her...
How you feeling, Accelerator?!
（木原）
元気かな？　アクセラレータ
ハハハハッ…
What the hell do you want, Kihara-kun?
何の用かな？　木原君
Hey, did you find a piece of that brat's clothing?
（木原）
なあ　その辺りにガキのシャツの
切れ端とか落ちてねえ？
If not, then try looking around.
まだだったら 捜してみろって
わざわざ残してやったんだからよ
I left it there just for you.
But man, this Testament thing is amazing!
それにしても
学習装置(テスタメント)ってのは すげえよな
It's not every day that you can bust a virus straight into a human's brain!
人間の頭に
ウイルスぶち込めるなんて―
普通じゃねえよ　ハハハハッ…
So, how should I react?
…で 俺は何て―
リアクションすりゃいいんだ？
Maybe laughing until my stomach hurts is the best choice for Mr. Masochist.
腹ぁ抱えて笑ってやんのが
正解かな？　マゾ太君
Hey, have you completely lost your cognitive faculties or something?
（木原）
おいおい てめえ　状況判断能力が
壊れちまってんのか？
And why won't you kill the brat?
そっちこそ
なんで あのガキを殺さねえ？
I doubt you or your cronies would normally even consider recovering her unharmed, right?
どうせ お前を雇ってるヤツは
“無傷で回収しろ”なんて―
涙あふれるセリフを
吐いちゃいねえよな？
にもかかわらず
ブルッちゃって―
Yet you're so chicken, you can't lay a finger on her.
指１本 触れられねえお前は
何なのよ？
Why is that?
I'll kill her.
（木原）殺す
（電話の切れる音）
I knew it.
やっぱりな
The normal Kihara I know would've plucked an eyeball from her if I'd said something like that in the past.
あの野郎の人格なら
ここまで言われりゃ―
あのガキの目玉のひとつくらいは
はじいてたはずだ
それがなかったってことは…
But the fact that he didn't means...
My, oh my. He's now officially a pawn.
おやおや…
こいつは本格的にパシリ確定かよ
There's someone in the shadows telling him exactly what to do.
あの木原を
思いとどまらせるほどのバック
Don't tell me he plans to use Academy City as a whole?
まさか 学園都市そのものか
Then, if I search among the Board of Directors...
なら 統括理事会
そっちを調べりゃ…
Hey, I'm pretty good, figuring out so much already.
ハハハッ… おいおい すげえな…
あっという間に進展しちまった
ハハハハッ…
You think you can really screw around with me?!
ふざけんじゃねえぞ！
（スイッチを入れる音）
ナメやがって！
Think again!
クッ… ハァ…
（ｱﾚｲｽﾀｰ）
うむ…
何やら 表が騒がしいようだが
Seems like there's some commotion outside.
The Imaginary District's Fifth Facility, which utilizes AIM diffusion fields, has completed its expansion.
ＡＩＭ拡散力場を利用した―
虚数学区 五行機関は展開完了した
If anybody uses magic within Academy City, they will go into overdrive and self-destruct.
この学園都市の内部で
魔術を行使すれば―
あらゆる魔術師は暴走 自爆する
Vento of the Front, was it?
前方のヴェントだったか…
それは貴様とて例外ではない
You are no exception.
The current output is not enough to cover the entire world,
現在の出力では
世界を覆うことはできない
but, with Fuse Kazakiri in the picture,
だが ヒューズ＝カザキリの
出番とともに―
the tables will turn.
形勢は そのまま逆転する
ハァ…
What in the world is this?
これは一体 何だ？
I've felt this strange presence for a while now...
さっきから この正体不明の気配
まだ膨らみ続けてる
I can still feel it, too...
てめえ！
なんで てめえが ここにいる？
You bitch...
Why are you here?!
You came all this way to die?
わざわざ殺されに来たってこと？
Where'd you take Last Order?
ラストオーダーをどこにやった！
"Last Order"?
ラストオーダーだ？
知らねえよ そんなもんは！
Hell if I know who that is!
（上条）あっ…
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）なに？
What?
ウワッ！
ンンッ… ヴェントは…
Where's Vento...
I see.
そうか…
So that's the Imaginary District's Fifth Facility.
これが虚数学区 五行機関の
全貌ってことか
You're off the hook for now.
てめえみてえな小物は後回しだ
Don't look down on us!
ナメやがって！
そうまでして私たちを―
You really think we'll let you mock us like that?!
おとしめたいか！
（打ちつける音）
She disappeared?
（上条）
消えた？
What was she looking at?
あいつは何を見ていたんだ？
No way...
ウソ …だろう？
The Imaginary District's Fifth Facility has begun its expansion.
（機械音声）
虚数学区 五行機関が展開を開始
Priority Individual, Last Order: Code authenticated.
上位個体 ラストオーダーは
コードを認証
Fuse Kazakiri will now manifest.
これより
ヒューズ＝カザキリが出現します
All related officials, please prepare for the shockwave.
関係各位は
不意の衝撃に備えてください
まさか… 天使？
Is that...
an angel?!
I shouldn't be here...
ここにいるとヤバそうだ
でも ラストオーダーは どこに…
Where's the hell's Last Order, though?!
Damn it!
ちくしょう
（プッシュ音）
Hey, I'm at the bridge, but I don't see Last Order anywhere.
なあ　鉄橋まで来たけど
ラストオーダーは いなかった
そっちは？
Have you found her?
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
フッ… バカじゃねえのか？
Are you an idiot?
You really fell for that?
そんなウソ 信じてんじゃねえよ
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
あのガキの居場所は
もうすぐ突き止められそうだ
I'll probably figure out her location soon.
少なくとも
走り回って見つかるとこにはいねえ
It's useless to run around the streets trying to find her.
I'll handle the rest.
あとは こっちでやる
お前は さっさと帰れ
Go home.
ンッ…
お前も見ただろう あの光の翼
You saw it too, right?
Those wings of light.
俺は
あの天使を止めなくちゃならない
I have to stop that angel.
So, helping you from now on will be difficult.
だから 本当に あんたと―
協力するのは難しくなる
I don't really care.
かまわねえ
Sorry.
悪い
Don't die.
（上条）死ぬなよ
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）互いにな
Same to you.
ンッ… とうとう
あれを使っちまったのか あの野郎
So he's finally resorted to that?
That bastard...
He's going to completely annihilate anyone in his way.
本気で敵を殲滅(せんめつ)する腹か
Signal from Serial Number 20001 confirmed.
（妹達(シスターズ)Ａ）
上位個体20001号より信号を確認
Assuming emergency state level 5.
（御坂(みさか)10032）
危険度５と推定
御坂10032号は拒絶
MISAKA-10032 will reject her.
（妹達Ｂ）
拒絶を認めず
ＲＶＹ経路で信号を受諾
Rejection failed.
Signal accepted through routes R, V, Y.
（妹達Ｃ）思考機能に重大な負荷
（妹達Ｄ）拒絶を認めず
Large loads on cognitive pathways detected.
Rejection failed.
We must act as best as we can without opposing the order.
（御坂10032）
命令にあらがわない範囲での行動を
If we can help overcome this critical situation...
それが結果的に
この危機的状況の打破につながれば
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
トマス＝プラチナバーグ
統括理事会12人のひとりか
Thomas Platinabank.
One of the 12 chairmen on the General Board of Directors.
Operation codename: Angel.
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）
“作戦コード名 ANGEL(エンジェル)”
In order to eliminate the unidentified threat,
“正体不明の脅威を取り除くために
ラストオーダーを回収”
we will recover Last Order and overwrite the virus to counter the threat.
“ウイルスを上書きして対抗する”
You've gotta be kidding.
ふざけやがって
I guess this means that the brat's still alive.
…てことは
まだ あのガキは生きてるはずだ
Where the hell are you hiding, Kihara?
木原の野郎 どこに隠れてる？
（美琴(みこと)）
どうなってんのよ？　あれ
What in the world is happening?
ちょっと！
こんなとこで何やってんのよ？
Hey!
What are you doing here?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
離して！　行かないと…
あそこには氷華(ひょうか)がいるの
Let go of me!
I have to go there.
Hyouka's there!
氷華？
Hyouka?
（上条）ハァハァ…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ダメだよ 当麻(とうま)！
Don't, Touma!
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）氷華を殺さないで！
（上条）ハッ…
Don't kill Hyouka!
Index?
（上条）インデックス… 御坂
（車のブレーキ音）
Misaka?
This way!
（上条）こっちだ
（美琴）ええっ？
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
お願い 当麻
あそこには行かないで
Please, Touma, don't go there!
あそこにいる天使は
きっと氷華なんだよ
The angel there is actually Hyouka!
あれが風斬(かざきり)？
That's Kazakiri?
I don't know what's happened to her, but you can't go there!
どういう理屈か
私にも よく分からないけど
当麻だけは関わっちゃダメ！
If you touch her, she'll disappear!
当麻が触ったら
氷華が消えちゃうんだよ
I'll do something about Hyouka, so please just leave her be—
氷華は私が なんとかするから
だから 氷華に手を出さないで！
（上条）ダメだ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）えっ？
No.
（上条）
あいつは俺が止める
それに 問題は あいつだけじゃない
I'll stop her.
Besides, she isn't the only problem right now.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
でも 当麻の右手を使ったら
氷華が死んじゃう
But if you use your right hand, she'll die...
I won't let her die!
（上条）死なせねえよ！
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ハッ…
I'm not going there to kill her, I'm going to save her!
殺すためじゃねえ　助けるために
立ち上がるっつってんだ
（上条）
あんなのが
普通の風斬に見えんのかよ？
Do you really think that's the normal Kazakiri?
そんなわけねえだろう
Of course not!
So I have to go and save her!
（上条）
だったら
助けないとダメだろうが！
行くぞ インデックス
Let's go, Index.
Lend me your strength to help save Kazakiri!
風斬を助けるために
お前の力を貸してくれ
（美琴）ハァ…
（上条）うん？
なんだか分からないけど
I don't really get it, but it sounds like you've gotten yourself into another huge mess.
また あんたは でかい問題に
巻き込まれてるってことなのね？
（美琴）
…で その中心点には
あんたの知り合いがいると
So, at the center of that thing is someone you know?
Not just someone. A friend.
知り合いじゃないよ　友達！
Just making sure, but she's not the bad guy, right?
ひとつだけ確認するけど
そいつは悪人じゃないのよね？
Of course not.
絶対 違う
Index said so too, right?
インデックスも言っただろう
あそこにいるのは俺の友達だ
That's our friend.
（美琴）
友達ね…
A friend...
So then, those are the bad guys?
じゃ あいつらが悪者ってわけね？
All right, then.
しゃあない
こっちは なんとかするから
I'll deal with them.
Wai—
（上条）お前…
（美琴）ごめん ごめん
Sorry, but I've already gotten started!
止める間もなく始めちゃうわよ！
Wh-What the...
（隊員）
な… 何だ？
（上条）御坂！
（美琴）罰ゲームよ
Misaka!
The penalty game!
Today isn't over yet.
今日１日 まだ有効だからね
I'm telling you to go save your friend and come back, no matter what!
あんたは
必ず 友達 助けて戻ってくること
Got it?
分かった？
I will!
必ず守る！
だから てめえも死ぬんじゃねえぞ
So, don't you die on me either!
I'm really stressed right now...
今 私は
とってもムシャクシャしてる！
Hey, Touma.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
ねえ 当麻
The city's so quiet because of that magician.
さっきから静かなのは
その魔術師のせいなんだね？
そうだ
そいつの攻撃の仕組みを知りたい
Yeah.
Tell me about the structure of her attack.
And if possible, a way to reverse it.
（上条）
治せる方法があるなら そいつもだ
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）多分 それは天罰だよ
（上条）なんだって？
It's probably "Divine Punishment."
What's that?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
ある感情をカギにしているの
It turns a specific emotion into a key.
Anyone who feels that emotion gets struck down, regardless of where they are.
その感情を抱いた者を―
距離や場所を問わずに
たたきつぶす　だから 天罰
Hence the name "Divine Punishment."
But Touma, did you see that magician act that way?
当麻　その魔術師は
そういう そぶりを見せなかった？
Like she was trying to incite a particular emotion from you?
必要以上に
特定の感情を誘導するような
A particular emotion?
特定の感情…
（上条）
嫌悪感… いや 敵意や悪意？
Unpleasantness?
No, hostility?
（上条）
まさか そいつが
その術式発動のカギなのか？
Is that the key to her magic's activation?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
うん　どの段階であっても―
Yes.
No matter what stage it's at, it cannot be reversed until the magician declares it over.
魔術師が
天罰は必要ないと判断するまで―
絶対に治らないと思う
じゃ 風斬の天使の仕組みは
どうなってる？
Then what about Kazakiri becoming an angel?
なあ　あいつは大丈夫なんだよな？
She's going to be okay, right?
I don't know!
分かんないよ
外観が似てる魔道書はあるけど
I have some grimoires that appear similar, but the parts being used are totally messed up.
使われてるパーツはメチャクチャ
見たこともない物ばっかりなんだよ
I've never seen any of them before.
少なくとも あそこにいる天使と
それを統率している核が―
I do know that the angel there and the core controlling it are in different locations.
別々の場所にあるのは
分かるんだけど
Well, Kazakiri is from the science side...
風斬は科学サイドだからな
Who are you calling, Touma?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
どうしたの？ 当麻
Damn it, no answer.
（上条）
くそ！　出ない
The most knowledgeable person besides Komoe-sensei would probably be...
小萌(こもえ)先生以外に詳しそうなのは…
（上条）御坂？
（美琴）ンッ… な… 何よ？
Misaka!
Wh-What is it?!
どうにかして あの天使を止めたい
お前だけが頼りなんだ
We have to stop that angel.
You're our only hope!
（携帯電話:銃撃音）
（美琴）ンッ！
おい 御坂！　撃たれたのか？
Hey, Misaka!
Are you hit?!
ち… 違うわよ
I'm not, but realize that you're making me use my head while I'm trying to fight...
別のことに頭使いながら戦えって
ホントに容赦ないわね あんた
You really don't let up, do you?
All right, Index, ask her anything you don't know!
（上条）
よし… インデックス
分からないことがあったら
全部 こいつに聞け
Oh, man, that's awesome!
（木原）
ハハッ！　すげえな おい！
ありゃ 一体 何なんだ？
What is it?
Damn, you're out of this world, Aleister!
（木原）
ちくしょう
飛んでやがんな アレイスター
理論の“り”の字も分かんねえぞ
I don't get any of the theory or logic behind it.
You're a scientist, and yet you're rejecting science...
科学者のくせに
科学を否定するとは―
なんたる科学者だよ
What kind of scientist is that?
見ろよ てめえら！　聖書ってのは
いつから 飛び出す絵本…
Check that out!
Since when did the Bible become a pop-up book—
Kihara-kun!!
木原くーん！
ほら ちゃんと撃てよ
じゃねえと みんなの迷惑だぜ！
Come on, shoot him already.
It's annoying for everyone when you don't!
（隊員）
ヒイッ！
（隊員）う… 動くな！
（ｱｸｾﾗﾚｰﾀ）ああ？
Don't move!
Damn, that's cool!
カッコイイ！
I might fall for you, Accelerator!
ホレちゃいそうだぜ
アクセラレータ
Now, then...
さ～て　スクラップの時間だぜ！
It's time to scrap!
You bastard!!
くそ野郎が！
（上条）
風斬…
Kazakiri...
Kazakiri!!
（上条）
風斬ーっ！
風斬！　ンッ…
Kazakiri!
Kazak—
かざき… ンッ…
クッ… ちくしょう！
（殴る音）
Damn it!
Well, well...
大罪人同士 傷のなめ合いでも
やってるとこだったかしら？
If it's not the fellow sinners.
Are you here to lick each other's wounds?
I even thought about leaving you for later, but you decided to come get killed?
せっかく後回しにしてやろうと
考えてたのに
自分から殺されに来ちゃったの？
フフッ… これ以上
悲惨なもんを見たくないから―
Or maybe you can't bear seeing that pathetic sight any longer, so you want me to crush you first?
先に
ぶっつぶしてほしいってことかな？
風斬は やらせない
I won't let you touch Kazakiri!
As one of God's Right Seat, I can't let such a monstrosity go.
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
私は神の右席の一員として―
そこの怪物を
見過ごすわけにはいかない
そいつは
科学によって生みだされた―
That thing is blasphemous filth born of science; it mocks all those who pray to the cross!
十字架を掲げる全ての人々を
あざ笑う冒涜(ぼうとく)の塊
You bitch! Take that back!
てめえ！　撤回しろ！
It's fine, I'll kill you as well.
（ｳﾞｪﾝﾄ）
じゃ いいわ　仲良く殺してあげる
Along with that demon!
そこの堕天使野郎と一緒にね！
（上条）
やらせるかよ
You think I'll let you?!
ただでさえ こんな目に遭わされて
She's suffering enough already without you calling her a monster and threatening to kill her!
その上 てめえみたいな人間に―
化け物扱いされたまま
殺されろだと？
Shut the hell up!
ふざけんじゃねえよ！
（上条）
人の友達を何だと思ってやがる！
You think I'd let you do that to my friend?!
～♪
Next episode
（上条）
それぞれの戦いは
更に激しさを増す
The various battles being fought become more heated.
What is Index's answer to this chaos born of science and magic?
科学と魔術が作り出した混沌(こんとん)の中で
インデックスが出した答えは…
次回 「天罰術式」
Next time: "Divine Punishment Spell Structure."
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる